Haisu Zhang

Assistant Professor of Marketing at Purdue University Calumet

Greater Chicago Area Higher Education

- 1. University of Illinois at Chicago
- 2. Walgreens
- 3. , China Sports Audiovisual
 - 1. MBA, Management at Purdue University Calumet

Education

Previous

169 connections

Connect

Send InMail

More options

• www.linkedin.com/pub/haisu-zhang/30/560/982

Contact Info

Summary

Haisu Zhang is an Assistant Professor of Marketing at Purdue University Calumet (PUC). He holds a Ph.D. degree in Business Administration (Marketing) from the University of Illinois at Chicago (UIC). He also received an MBA degree from PUC and a bachelor degree in Business Management from Beijing Technology and Business University. Prior to joining PUC, Haisu was an instructor of marketing and research assistant at UIC. Haisu's research and teaching interests include product innovation, marketing strategy, interorganizational marketing, and international business. His work has been published in the Journal of International Marketing, and presented at American Marketing Association Winter/Summer Marketing Educators' Conference, Annual Global Conference on Product Innovation Management, and Annual Society for Industrial and Organizational Psychology Conference.

Specialties

Research on innovation, new product development, international business, knowledge management, and organizational learning; statistical techniques of structural equation modeling and hierarchical linear modeling; teaching interests in marketing strategy, international marketing, product/brand management, B2B marketing, and marketing research methods

Experience

Assistant Professor of Marketing

Purdue University Calumet

Educational Institution; 501-1000 employees; Higher Education industry

August 2012 - Present (4 months) Hammond, IN

Haisu has 3 recommendations (3 co-workers) including:

- 2nd Tim Basadur, Doctoral student and lecturer, University of Illinois at Chicago
- 2nd Esi A. Elliot, PhD Candidate, University of Illinois at Chicago

Doctoral Student and Instructor

University of Illinois at Chicago Report this position

Educational Institution; 10,001+ employees; Higher Education industry

August 2007 - August 2012 (5 years 1 month) Greater Chicago Area

Haisu has 2 recommendations (2 clients) including:

- 2nd Michael Baer 2nd Todd Turner Jr

Assistant Manager

Walgreens

Public Company; 10,001+ employees; WAG; Retail industry

2006 – 2006 (less than a year)

Handled daily cash flow including: reconciling, balancing, and depositing Assessed and maintained inventory Mediated issues between customers and employees Served customers based on their specific and individual needs

Marketing Assistant

China Sports Audiovisual

2003 – 2004 (1 year) Beijing, China

Initiated sales plans including: budget, price, sales forecast, and distribution Solved customer complaints and provided excellent customer service Managed inventory by receiving and filling orders promptly

Skills & Expertise Endorsements Learn more

1. 2 Marketing Research



3.

2. 1 Marketing



Education

Purdue University Calumet

MBA, Management

2004 - 2006

Activities and Societies: President, International Students Organization

University of Illinois at Chicago

Ph.D., Marketing

2007

Activities and Societies: Representative, Graduate Student Council

Haisu has 1 recommendation including:

• 2nd Ryan Gensler, Student, University of Illinois at Chicago